Aaron Magder

Hamilton, ON (289)-780-8981 aaron@magder.me

Summary

Hard working self-motivator with many years of experience in the IT field. Currently holds a 96% average at Mohawk College with expectation to graduate by the end of 2015. Demonstrated strong technical skills and out-of-box problem solving. Proven leadership experience.

Education

Network Engineering and IT Security Analyst Advanced Diploma

Mohawk College (2012-2015)
In progress (one semester remaining). Current GPA of 96%

over 5 semesters. Been named to Dean's Honour List each semester.

Experience

ePortfolio Assistant

(Sep 2015 - Current)

nt) Web design of online portfolios.

IT Technician

(Apr 2015 - Sep 2015)

Halton Hills Hydro

Mohawk College

Troubleshooting a variety of issues on a small business network (approx 50 users). Backend support and server maintenance. Provided analysis of IDS reports. Designed an IDS. Developed software and web applications. Assisted with mobile device

configuration.

Service Desk Analyst

(Apr 2014 – Sep 2014)

Ministry of Government Services

Troubleshooting a variety of issues on a large enterprise network

(approx 10,000 users). Fulfillment of service requests.

(Nov 2010 - Sep 2012)

Bell Mobility

Troubleshooting a variety of issues for end users for a mobile service provider. Assisting internal agents with enterprise tools.

Skills

I am highly skilled in networking, security and administration of Windows/Linux networks. I have experience with a wide variety of technologies. If you'd like further detail about specific skillsets feel free to contact me.

TCP/IP Networking			
Network Security			
Windows Administration			
Linux Administration			
Mobile Devices			
Scripting/Programming/Web Dev			

Certifications and Awards

Comptia A+ Certification2008Part 2 Winner – IBM Master the Mainframe Challenge2014Offensive Security Certified Practitioner (OSCP)In Progress

Additional Information

To view more information or to connect with me on social media visit:



http://magder.me